我还会想到那个晚上
I still think about the night
你母亲和我不得不离开你
your mother and I had to leave you.
希望能快去快回
Hopefully, it's not for long,
我们安顿好了会打给你的
but I'll call you when we get settled.
等我更了解情况了的
When I have a better indication of what's going on.
妈妈
Mommy?
小糖豆
Jellybean.
爸爸和我要临时出趟差
Daddy and I have a last-minute business trip...
萝丝会在这里陪你几天
so Rose is gonna stay with you for a few days.
不要  我不要你走
No. I don't want you to go.
肯定可无聊了
It's gonna be so boring.
我会困得睁不开
I won't be able to keep my...
眼睛
eyes...
再见  亲爱的  我们很快就回来
Goodbye, sweetheart. All right, we'll see you soon.
好
Okay.
珍妮特  我们得走了
Janet, we gotta go.
真希望我们能够放下行李
I wish we could have put down our bags...
哄你上床
tucked you back into your bed...
但这事关太多性命
but too many lives were at stake.
天呐
Oh, my God.
已经发射了
They've already launched.
我们得拦截它
We have to stop it.
走吧
Come on.
要拆除导弹  我们必须进去
To disarm the missile, we had to get inside it...
但外壳太厚了
but the plating was too thick.
如果想进去  只能缩小  钻过分子间隙
The only way in was to shrink between the molecules.
我钻不透
I can't get through.
汉克
Hank.
我们都清楚  如果缩小到那个程度
We both knew that if you go that small...
就回不来了
there is no coming back.
本该是我去的  但我的调节器坏了
It should have been me, but my regulator was damaged.
你妈妈的还完好
Your mother's wasn't.
告诉霍普我爱她
Tell Hope I love her.
她关掉了它
She turned it off.
珍妮特  不要
Janet. No!
进入了亚原子状态好拆弹
She went subatomic to deactivate the bomb.
你母亲那天拯救了上千人的性命
Your mother saved thousands of lives that day
尽管她知道  她会迷失在量子域中
knowing she'd be lost in the quantum realm.
孤身一人
Alone.
害怕恐惧
Afraid.
永远迷失
Gone forever.
告诉你她再不能回家
Telling you that she wasn't coming home...
是我这辈子做过的最难的事
was the hardest thing that I ever had to do.
但后来斯科特出现了
But then Scott showed up.
或者该说  他闯进了我们家
Or should I say, broke into our house.
他进入量子域后
And when he went to the quantum realm...
却又回来了
and came back.
一切都变了
Everything changed.
我开始想
I started to wonder...
或许你妈妈还活着
could your mother still be alive?
所以我翻出了一些旧图纸
So, I dusted off some old plans.
爸爸  你是什么意思
Dad, what are you saying?
我们或许能救她回来
I think it's possible to bring her back.
好  我们进来了
Okay. We're in.
现   今
这地方就是个迷宫
Oh, this place is a maze.
地图呢
Where's that map?
我们绝对接近了
We're definitely close.
-准备好了吗  -好了  爸爸
- You ready? - I'm ready, Daddy.
确定吗  等我们进去了
Are you sure? 'Cause once we're inside,
如果你迟疑或害怕  我们就死定了
you show any hesitation or fear, we're done.
我拿恐惧当早餐吃
I eat fear for breakfast.
这太酷了
That is super cool.
来吧
Come on.
看  是安东  他会给我们指路的
Look! It's Anton. He'll show us the way.
安东  我们走哪边
Anton, which way do we go?
谢谢  安东
Thanks, Anton!
看啊  蚂蚁打通进了科技设施
Look, the ants have burrowed into the tech facility.
不  激光
Oh no, lasers!
我好像碰到了激光
I think I got lased!
秘密宝库
The secret vault.
你带隐形眼镜来了吧
Tell me you brought the contact lens.
带了
Yup.
完美  对准那里
Perfect! Right there.
找到了  是微宝藏
There! It's the micro-treasure!
我的奖杯
My trophy?
看上去像宝藏
It looks like treasure.
对我来说是的
Oh, it is to me.
我想拿去做展示说明
I want to take it to show-and-tell.
那不行
Oh, no, you can't do that.
不行  它绝不能离开这栋房子
You can't. It never leaves the house.
它太重要了
It's too important.
这是你给我的最棒的生日礼物
This is the best birthday present you ever got me.
我觉得好感动
I'm so touched
你认为我是世界上最棒的奶奶
you think I'm the world's greatest grandma.
世界上最棒的奶奶
他们只有这一个了
It was the only one they had.
让我好想给你织件毛衣
It makes me want to knit you a sweater.
不  是条子
Oh, no, the fuzz!
斯科特
Hey, Scotty...
我在看卡拉佩特安大楼的图纸
I was looking at the schematics for the Karapetyan buildings...
我觉得我们装了太多的监控摄像头
and I think we have way too many security cameras, don't we?
完全没有
No, no, not at all.
因为  摄像头真的好多
I mean, 'cause it's a lot of security cameras.
我知道他需要什么
I know what he needs.
我们公司的安保专家是谁啊
Who's the security expert in our business?
是你  但经营公司的是我
You are, but I'm running the company, right?
如果我们开价太高
And if we overquote him...
他会去别家的
he's gonna go somewhere else.
我们一定要让这只大鸟到手
I mean, we gotta land this bird.
他不会去别家的
He ain't goin' anywhere.
而且那句俗语是"大鱼到手"
And the expression is "Land this fish."
不  是"大鸟到手"
No, it's "Land the bird."
就像"飞机到站"嘛
Just like you land the plane.
你得"飞机到站"才能维系生意
You gotta land the plane to be in business.
我知道纠结这种事挺傻的
I know it's silly to get hung up on these kinds of things,
-但我就这样  -鱼怎么能到手
- but I do. - How am I gonna land a fish?
它又不能走  如果它游上岸
It can't walk. And if it swam up on shore
跟鹰打一架  谁会赢
and it battled a hawk, who's gonna win?
这件事我真被你说服了
You've really turned me around on this thing.
没事  我们会把卡拉佩特安拿到手的
It's okay. We're gonna land Karapetyan.
失陪了
Now, if you just excuse me...
我正在跟女儿偷东西呢
I'm in the middle of trying to steal something with my daughter.
我去重查一遍
I'm gonna go recheck it.
去找逃脱蚁
To the escape ant!
趁条子还没回来  我们赶紧跑
Let's bounce before the po-po come back!
条子  这些词你都哪学的
The po-po? How do you even know that?
飞吧  安托瓦内特  飞吧
Let's fly, Antoinette! Let's fly!
硬着陆
Crash landing!
真希望我们能真缩小
I wish we could shrink for real.
那是挺酷的
That is pretty cool.
我去办公室了  斯科特
I'm headed to the office, Scotty.
抱歉我之前抓狂了
And sorry about freaking out earlier, you know.
但我觉得我好多了
But I feel like I'm way better.
我的心绝对跳得太快了
My heart is definitely beating way too hard and stuff.
我的手也在抖
And my hands are shaking.
但应该跟这没关系的吧
But I think it's unrelated, you know?
肯定很棒的  路易斯
It's gonna be great, Luis!
你完全不用担心
You got nothing to worry about!
是啊  我是老大  我最棒了
Yeah, yeah. I'm the boss. I'm the boss.
我最厉害  好好好
I'm the boss. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
爸爸
Daddy!
拜托  吴  我只剩三天了
Come on, Woo! I've got three days left.
我为什么要企图逃跑
Why would I try to escape?
抱歉  斯科特  规矩就是规矩
Sorry, Scott, but rules are rules.
你触发了边界警报  我们就搜屋
You trip the perimeter alarm, we search the place.
角角落落都得搜到
Keel to stern, soup to nuts.
谢谢
Thank you.
就是个意外  我的脚穿透了栅栏
It was an accident. My foot went through the fence.
我们的飞蚁硬着陆了
Our flying ant crashed.
你试试在不能出屋的情况下
Hey, you try and entertain a 10-year-old
逗一个10岁小孩
when you can't leave the house.
知道我多努力吗
You know the lengths that I've gone to?
近景魔术
Close-up magic.
我学的
I learned that.
你为什么就不能放过我爸爸
Why can't you just leave my daddy alone?
凯西
Oh, Cassie.
这一切一定让你觉得像是
This must all seem like a bunch of
令人困惑的大人的事吧
confusing grown-up stuff to you, huh?
这么想吧
Well, think of it this way.
你们学校有校规吧
Your school has rules, right?
比如  不能在墙上乱涂乱画
Like, you can't draw on the walls.
你爸爸去了德国
Well, your daddy went to Germany
跟美国队长在墙上乱涂乱画来着
and drew on the walls with Captain America.
这违反了《索科威亚协议》
And that was a violation of Article 16,
第16款第三条
Paragraph Three of the Sokovia Accords.
按照他与国土安全部
Now, as a part of his joint plea deal
和德国政府签订的联合认罪协议
with Homeland Security and the German government
他可以回到美国
he was allowed to return to the U.S
前提是他服两年的软禁刑期
provided he serve two years under house arrest
和三年的假释
followed by three years of probation.
且不得擅自行动或使用未获批设备
And avoid any unauthorized activities, technology
或接触任何曾经
or contact with any former associates
或正在违反前述协议或任何相关法规的
who were or currently are in violation of said Accords.
旧同伙
Or any related statutes.
懂了吗  亲爱的
Okay, sweetie?
你还真会带小孩
You're really great with kids.
谢谢  我兼职做青年牧师的
Thanks. I'm also a youth pastor.
总之  不是我包打听
Anyway, not to be a Johnny ask-a-lot
但你最近没联系过
but you haven't had any contact
汉克·皮姆和霍普·凡·戴恩吧
with Hank Pym or Hope Van Dyne, have you?
-没有  -真的吗
- No. - You sure?
因为我们迟早会抓到他们
Because it's only a matter of time before we get 'em.
那是他们的设备  所以他们也违反了协议
It was their tech, so they violated the Accords, too.
跟他们有联系是违反你的认罪协议的
And associating with them breaks your deal.
不用我提醒你
And, uh, I don't need to remind you
若对认罪协议有丝毫违反
that any violation of your agreement
就是至少20年的监狱刑期
means 20 years in prison. Minimum.
我好久没跟汉克和霍普联系过了
I haven't talked to Hank or Hope in forever.
他们恨死他了
They hate his guts.
谢谢  小花生
Thanks, peanut.
你怎么做到的  斯科特
How'd you do it, Scott?
做什么
Do what?
纸牌戏法
The card trick.
不是吧
Seriously?
天呐
Oh, my God!
你们不能高兴了就跑来
You people can't just show up here whenever you want
然后搜查这里
and search the place.
其实  他们可以的
Actually, they can.
你需要搜查令
You need a warrant.
其实  他们不需要
Actually, they don't.
真的吗
Really?
带足球鞋了吗
Did you pack your soccer shoes?
-嗯  -好
- Yeah. - All right.
下次我再见你  就是在外面了
Next time I see you will be on the outside.
好
All right.
我也要抱抱
Get on the inside of this.
三天了  真的
Hey, three days. Seriously...
-为你骄傲  哥们  -谢谢
- I'm proud of you, bud. - Thank you.
知道吗  再来一个
You know what? Give me another one.
我也是  天呐  自由
Me too! Gosh! Freedom!
新生意  我觉得你前途无量
New business! I am sensing greatness.
我这周末很开心  爸爸
I had a fun weekend, Daddy.
我也是  小花生  等下周末的
Me too, peanut. But just wait till next weekend.
等我能出屋了  我们要出去疯玩
Once I'm outta here, you and I are gonna go paint this town red.
我们要吃一大堆冰淇淋  然后吐个不停
We'll have so much ice cream, we'll never stop puking.
你越来越厉害了
You're gettin' good at that.
怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
-再见  爸爸  -再见
- Bye, Daddy. - Bye.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
三天
Three days.
轻松
Easy-peasy.
线上近景魔术大学
打指响  让他们看这边
Snap your fingers. That gets them to look over there.
这叫做误导
And that is misdirection.
我们曾梦想
We had a dream
会一起去旅行
We'd go travelin' together
我们散播一点爱意  然后继续向前
We'd spread a little lovin' then we'd keep movin' on
星运里的错
卡拉佩特安公寓楼
轻松
Easy-peasy.
你在哪
Where are you?
你所知的一切
Everything that you know...
迷失在
Lost...
量子域里
in the quantum realm.
什么
What?
我要找到你  小糖豆
I'm gonna find you, Jellybean.
我找到你了
I found you!
你总能找到我  妈妈
You always find me, Mommy.
怎么回事
What the hell?
汉克  好久没联系了
Hank! It's been a while.
我都不知道这是否还是你的号码
I don't even know if this is your number anymore.
我可能是你最不想联系的人了
And I'm probably the last person you wanna hear from. But
但我刚做了个特奇怪的梦
I just had a really weird dream.
我知道这听上去不像是什么急事
And I know that doesn't sound like an emergency or anything...
但感觉特别真实
but it just felt very real.
我又回到了量子域
I was back in the quantum realm...
我觉得我看到了你妻子
and I think I saw your wife.
然后我变成你妻子了
And then I was your wife.
不是什么奇怪的意思
I mean, not in a weird way or anything.
其实  我这么说出来
You know, hearing this out loud,
我开始觉得  这事真不急
I'm thinking, uh, it's not an emergency.
抱歉打扰你了
I'm sorry to bother you.
我对很多事都感到抱歉
I'm sorry for a lot of things.
就是说  我手指甲上的一颗小原子
That means, one tiny atom in my fingernail
-就可能...  -可能是个
- could be... - Could be one, little,
小宇宙
tiny universe.
霍普
Hope?
这又是梦吗
Is this another dream?
你觉得那是梦吗
Do you think it was a dream
还是说你真有可能在那里看到了我妈妈
or is it possible that you really saw my mom down there?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我不能在这儿
I can't be here!
我不能在这儿  我在服软禁刑期
I can't be here! I'm under house arrest!
系统运行时是打不开的  斯科特
They won't open while the system's engaged, Scott.
你得带我回家  他们随时可能会上门
You have to take me home. They could show up any second!
放松  就你的保姆警察所知
Relax. As far as your nanny cops know,
你还在家呢
you're still at home.
斯科特
Scotty?
他已被编程好复制你的日常活动
He's programmed to replicate your daily routine.
九小时睡觉
Nine hours in bed.
五小时看电视
Five hours in front of the TV.
两小时泡在厕所  不管是为啥
Two hours in the bathroom, whatever that's about.
这根本不准确
That's totally inaccurate.
你怎么会知道我的日常活动
And how do you know about my daily routine?
你在监视我吗
Are you spying on me?
我们注意一切安全隐患
We keep tabs on all security threats, all right?
而目前为止  你是最大一个
And so far the biggest one we've had is you.
德国的事我很抱歉  是他们跑来找我
I'm sorry about Germany. They just showed up.
还说事关国家安全
They said it was a matter of national security.
美队需要帮助  所以...
That Cap needed help, so...
美队
Cap?
...国队长  美国队长  美队
Tain America. Captain. Cap.
我们就这么喊他
It's what we call him.
朋友之间
If you're a friend.
我倒不是说我算是朋友...算是吧
I'm not saying I'm a friend of... A little,
我认识他  他人挺好  不说了
I know him. He's nice. Whatever.
对不起  好吗  我没想到我会被抓
I'm sorry! All right? I didn't think I'd get caught.
你没想的事多了
You didn't think about a lot of things.
汉克怎么样
How's Hank?
我们还在逃跑
We're still running.
房子没了  我们的自由也没了
The house is gone, so is our freedom.
你觉得他会怎么样
How do you think he is?
对不起  我知道你生我气
I'm sorry. I know you're mad.
我要的不是道歉  斯科特
I'm not looking for an apology, Scott.
我之所以还跟你说话
The only reason why we're even talking is
是因为我们需要你脑子里的东西
because we need what's in your head.
这是你们住的地方吗
Is this where you're living?
如果你们需要帮助或钱  或许我可以...
If you need help or money or something, maybe I can...
不用
We're fine.
汉克  听着  我只想...
Hank. Look, I just wanna...
省省吧
Save it!
-可以开始了吗  -是的
- Can we start? - Yeah.
你在家放松的时候
So, while you were relaxing at home
我们建了这个
we were building this.
是个隧道  通往量子域
It's a tunnel. To the quantum realm.
去找我妈妈
To my mom.
我们认为她可能还在那里
We think she might still be down there.
但我们不知道在哪
We just don't know where.
什么
What?
如果我们能定位出我妈的位置
If we can pinpoint my mom's location...
那我就能开驾驶舱去救她
then the pod can take me down to get her.
你们建造了这一切
You built all this
却都不能确定她是不是还活着吗
and you don't even know if she's alive?
这叫假设
It's called a hypothesis.
昨晚我们第一次启动了隧道
Last night, we powered up the tunnel for the first time.
但过载于是关停了
It was overloaded and it shut down.
但就在那一瞬间
But for a split second,
通往量子域的大门被打开了
the doorway to the quantum realm was opened.
然后呢
And?
五分钟后  你打了来  说起了我妈妈
And five minutes later, you called, talking about Mom.
我们认为你去那下面时
We think when you were down there,
可能跟她发生了纠缠
you may have entangled with her.
汉克  我绝不会那么做的
Hank, I would never do that.
我是尊重你的
I respect you too much.
量子纠缠  斯科特
Quantum entanglement, Scott.
我们认为她可能
We think she might have
在你脑袋里放了某种信息
put some kind of a message in your head.
希望是个位置信息
Hopefully, a location.
打开隧道时  信息被触发了
And opening the tunnel triggered it.
你妈妈在我脑袋里留了信息
Your mom put a message in my head?
拜托  这疯了
Come on. That's insane.
不  斯科特
No, Scott.
疯狂
Insane
是不告诉我们就跑去德国跟复仇者联盟打架
is going to Germany without telling us, and fighting the Avengers.
告诉我  关于你偷的战衣  你没撒谎
Just tell me you weren't lying about the suit you took.
告诉我你确实销毁了它
Tell me you really destroyed it.
是的  我销毁了它  我发誓
I did, I destroyed it, I swear.
我真不敢相信你销毁了我的战衣
I can't believe you destroyed my suit!
那可是我的毕生心血
That was my life's work!
我还能怎么办
What was I supposed to do?
你就不该偷走我的战衣
You were supposed to not take my suit!
对不起  汉克
I'm sorry, Hank!
对不起我偷走了战衣
I'm sorry I took the suit.
对不起我昨晚打了电话
I'm sorry that I called last night.
我不记得在下面见过珍妮特
I don't remember seeing Janet down there.
我也希望我见过
I wish that I did.
我就是梦到了她
I just had a dream about her
跟一个小姑娘玩捉迷藏
playing hide-and-seek with a little girl.
什么
What?
我梦到
I had a dream.
她在跟个小姑娘玩捉迷藏
She was playing hide-and-seek with a little girl.
凯西和我以前常玩的
Cassie and I do it all the time.
没什么意义
Doesn't mean anything.
但梦里的是凯西吗
But was it Cassie in the dream?
不是
No.
她藏在了哪里
Where was she hiding?
-什么  -那个小姑娘
- What? - The little girl.
她藏在了哪里  大衣柜吗
Where was she hiding? Was it in a wardrobe?
不是  是个很大的柜子
No, it was in a tall dresser.
就是衣柜咯
You mean a wardrobe.
是这么叫的吗
Is that what that's called?
什么颜色的
What color was it?
红的
Red.
上面有小马吗
Were there horses on it?
天呐
Oh, boy.
我们玩时  我每次都藏在那里
It's where I hid every time that we played.
听上去
It doesn't sound like
你没太理解这游戏的要义
you really got the gist of the game.
她还活着
She's alive.
我就知道
I knew it.
I knew it!
我们得拿到那个部件
We need to get that part.
好
Okay.
我们越早让隧道正常运作
The sooner we get the tunnel working...
就能越早从他脑袋里提取到信息
the sooner we can get this message out of his head.
伯奇拿到了吗
Does Burch have it?
-是的  我们走  -什么部件
- Yeah. Let's go. - What part?
伯奇是谁  等等  什么情况啊
Who's Burch? Wait. What's happening?
我们需要一个部件
We need a component
来防止隧道再次过载
to stop the tunnel from overloading again.
我帮你拿了衣服  你最好换一下
I grabbed your clothes. You might want to change.
听着  我也想帮你们
Look, I'd really like to help you...
但如果他们来给我摘脚环时我不在家
but if I'm not at home when they come to take off my ankle monitor
那我就要蹲一辈子了
then I'm going away forever.
等我们拿到了部件  启动了隧道
Once we get the component and power up the tunnel
就能拿到信息  你午饭前就能回到家
we'll get the message, and have you home by lunch.
我们得快点  纠缠不会维持太久
We have to hurry. The entanglement won't last.
你欠我们的
You owe us.
好吧  我能不能进去等
All right, fine. But can I just wait inside?
因为我不该在外面的
Because I'm not supposed to be out here.
走吧
Let's go.
-没问题吧  -嗯
- We good? - Yeah.
我就回来
I'll be right back.
-我能吃个吗  -不能
- Can I have one of these? - No.
苏珊  欢迎来到好餐厅
Susan! Welcome to Oui!
桑尼
Sonny!
"好"是法语"是"的意思
Oui is French for "Yes."
立意就是  是从农场直接上餐桌的本地好料
As in "Yes" to farm-to-table, "Yes" to locally sourced...
是把生态摆在利益之前的好策略
and "Yes" to planet before profit.
那希望"你是否拿到了
Well, let's hope it also means "Yes"
我订购的部件"的答案也是"是"
to "Do you have the component I ordered?"
我一向喜欢你的幽默感  苏珊
You know, I have always loved your sense of humor, Susan.
请坐
Have a seat.
不用了  谢谢
No, I'm good. Thank you.
这人是谁
Who is this guy?
桑尼·伯奇  黑市科技走私贩
Sonny Burch. He traffics in black market technology.
他为我们取得了建造隧道需要的材料
He's been getting us what we need to build the tunnel.
能给我一个...
Could I just have one...
不能
No.
我在联调局有个特别的朋友
You know, I have a special friend at the FBI.
我说"特别"是因为
And I say "Special" because,
他会告诉我些我原本不知道的事
well, he tells me things that I didn't previously know.
比如说
For example...
你名字不叫苏珊
your name isn't Susan.
而是霍普·凡·戴恩
It's Hope Van Dyne.
而你背后的同伙是你父亲  汉克·皮姆
And your unseen associate, that's your father, Hank Pym.
-这可不妙  汉克  -还用你说
- That's not good, Hank. - No shit.
你想要什么
What do you want?
关系是建立在信任上的  霍普
Relationships are built on trust, Hope.
我希望我们的关系有坚实的基础
And I want our relationship to have a strong foundation.
我们的关系
Our relationship?
我的市场在变化  霍普
My business landscape has been shifting, Hope.
神盾局和九头蛇都不存在了
Hell, S.H.I.E.L.D. and HYDRA don't even exist anymore...
但汉克·皮姆呢
but now, Hank Pym...
汉克·皮姆是个好机会
Hank Pym is a real opportunity.
你到底想说什么
Do you have a point?
你以为我不知道
Oh, you think that I don't know
你要这些是在建造什么吗
what you've been building with all this?
量子科技
Quantum technology.
什么纳米科技啊  人工智能啊
Now, you can forget nanotech, forget AI,
加密货币都过时了
forget cryptocurrency.
量子科技才是未来
Quantum energy is the future.
是下一阵淘金热
It's the next gold rush.
是吗
Is that so?
我要加入  霍普
I want in, Hope.
所以  出于好意  我已经擅自
So, as a gesture of good will, I have taken the liberty
为你的实验室安排了买家
of arranging some buyers for your lab.
起价
Starting bid
是十亿美金
one billion dollars.
谢谢  桑尼  真的
Thank you, Sonny, really.
但我父亲和我有件
But my father and I have something
比成立公司要更紧急的事
slightly more pressing than starting a business.
所以我还是按说好的拿走部件
So I'll just take the component as arranged.
我的买家不接受拒绝
My buyers don't take no for an answer.
所以  我们要么一起做生意
So, we are either in business together
要么就不做生意了
or we aren't in business together.
那就不做吧
Then I guess we aren't.
你可以走
You can go.
但你的钱恐怕得留下
But I'm afraid your money's gonna have to remain.
就当是赔偿我受伤的感情
Let's call it compensation for my injured feelings.
听着  桑尼
Listen, Sonny.
如果你痛快把部件给我
This is gonna be so much easier on everybody
对大家都会简单得多
if you just give me that component.
亲爱的  你唯一可以拿走的
Darlin', the only thing you're takin' from here...
就是我的心  但它会渐渐愈合的
is my heart, but it will mend in time.
好吧
Okay.
现在怎么办
So, now what?
等着瞧
You'll see.
她说她和她爸有什么要紧事
She said her and her daddy had something pressing.
我要知道是什么事
I want to know what it is
因为如果他们没在跟我们合作
because if they're not working with us
就肯定在跟别人合作
they're working with somebody.
去查明  我要知道名字
So find out. I want some names...
等等  你给她加了翅膀
Hold on, you gave her wings?
抓到她
Get her.
别打碎我的世纪之交大吊灯
Not my turn-of-the-century chandelier!
别开枪了  住手
Stop firing! Stop!
好吧  拿上这个  快走
All right, take this. Go. Go, go, go!
快走
Go!
翅膀还有爆能枪
Wings and blasters.
看来我那时候这技术还没开发好咯
So I take it you didn't have that tech available for me.
开发好了
No, I did.
很高兴跟你做生意  桑尼
It was a pleasure doing business with you, Sonny.
我们的事还没完呢  霍普
Oh, our business isn't finished yet, Hope.
我可以向你保证
I can assure you of that!
那是什么
What in the hell is that?
爸爸  你看到了吗
Dad, are you seeing this?
霍普  快跑
Hope, get out of there!
-我得做点什么  -等等
- I gotta do something. - Wait!
还没完成
It is still a work in progress.
那一踢是你教我的  记得吗
You taught me that kick. Remember?
嗯  姿势很棒
Yeah, great form.
想当年啊  我们是怎么了
Those were the days. Whatever happened to us?
不是时候  斯科特
Not the time, Scott.
该死  它哪去了
Damn it, where'd it go?
我跟丢了
I've lost it.
蚂蚁摄像头上什么都看不到
I'm not seeing anything on the ant cams.
去看看...
Try looking...
爸爸
Dad?
把那个给我
Give me that.
快点
Now.
-你没事吧  -有事
- Are you okay? - No!
他拿了实验室
He got the lab.
-不  -快走
- No. - Come on!
那是什么
What was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我们得找个地方重新部署
But we need to find somewhere to regroup
并查明实验室在哪
and figure out where the lab is.
现在去哪
So, where to now?
我家吧
How about my house?
我反正也该在那儿的
I'm supposed to be there anyway,
吴随时都可能到
and Woo could walk in any second.
所以我们绝不能去你家
Exactly why we're not going to your house.
那你家呢
What about your house?
抱歉
Sorry.
那我只能想到一个地方了
Well, there is one place I can think of.
不
No.
不不
No, no, no, no!
不
No!
前科范安保顾问公司
皮姆博士
Dr. Pym
谁能想到
like, who would've thought that,
您再次在危难时刻
once again, in your hour of need
找到了我们
that you would turn to us, you know?
我是没想到
Not me.
自便
Help yourself.
干吗买这么高档的点心
What's up with the fancy pastry?
我们得控制食物预算
We gotta keep the food budget down.
那我们早餐该吃什么
Well, what are we supposed to have for breakfast?
燕麦片
The oatmeal packets.
Oatmeal packets.
-这是侮辱  -怎么是侮辱了
- It's insult. - Why is it an insult?
因为那味道像沙子
Because it tastes like sand.
知道为什么吗  因为那是有机食品
You know why? 'Cause it's organic.
不是有机食品  是沙子
It's not organic, it's sand.
那可是一天最重要的一餐
It's the most important meal of the day.
你可以随意发挥嘛
You know what, you can get creative with it.
能硌断牙
Break teeth.
撒点红糖  撒点肉桂
Put a little brown sugar on it. You can put some cinnamon.
倒点蜂蜜
Put a little honey.
-随心所欲  -伙计们
- Whatever you want... - Guys, guys, guys.
干什么啊
Come on, man.
我们还有更要紧的事呢
We got bigger fish to fry.
那是我的桌子吗
Is that my desk?
-是的  -什么
- Yeah. - What?
为什么我的桌子那么小
Why do I have such a small desk?
斯科特
因为我们选桌子时你又不在
Because you weren't there when we were choosing desks.
打瞌睡就算你输
You snooze, you lose.
我在被软禁啊
Well, I was under house arrest.
是啊
Yeah.
知道吗  这都算不上是桌子
You know what, this isn't even a desk.
这是垃圾
This is garbage.
你们是在外面的垃圾里找来的
You found this outside amongst garbage.
那是我在旧物义卖上淘来的
I got it at a rummage sale.
你就偏在我的桌子上省钱
So, you save money on my desk?
行了
Guys.
霍普  拜托  我们得集中精神
Hope, please, we need to focus, all right?
我们得赶紧找到那个实验室  天呐
We gotta find that lab already. Jeez.
知道吗  我听说了你的遭遇
Oh, you know what? I heard stories, like what happened to you.
说有个吓人的家伙  能钻墙
This crazy, creepy cat, who walks through walls and stuff.
像个幽灵
Like a ghost.
像雅加婆婆
Like Baba Yaga.
雅加婆婆  女巫
Baba Yaga, the witch.
他们给小孩子讲故事吓唬他们
They tell stories to children to frighten them.
你知道雅加婆婆吗
You know Baba Yaga?
不管是谁偷的
Whoever stole it...
我们得找到它
we need to find it.
那样的人是找不到的  得等他们找你
Oh, you don't find someone like that. They find you.
就像雅加婆婆
Like Baba Yaga.
皮姆博士  你是我认识的最聪明的天才
Dr. Pym, you're the smartest genius I know.
你没有在实验室上安装寻回系统吗
Didn't you put some kind of LoJack on your lab?
因为如果你没有
Because if you didn't,
我们这里有很多价钱公道的选择
we have a variety of affordable options.
我当然安装了  路易斯
Of course I did, Luis.
系统被解除了
It was disabled.
偷走实验室的人非常在行
Whoever stole the lab knew exactly what they were doing.
那人看上去好像还在变相
They also looked like they were phasing.
变相
Phasing?
量子变相
Quantum phasing.
就是物体在物质的各状态间变化
When an object moves through different states of matter.
是啊  我想的也是那个
Oh, yeah, that's what I was thinking.
实验室释放辐射
The lab emits radiation.
我们可以改造一台量子光谱仪追踪它吗
Can we modify a quantum spectrometer and track it?
那是可行的  但我的设备都在实验室里
That could work, yes, but all my equipment is in the lab.
还有哪里有那样的设备
Where else can we find that equipment?
是有那么个人
Well, there is one person.
比尔·福斯特
Bill Foster.
好啊
Great!
那是谁
Who's Bill Foster?
他是我爸爸的一个老同事  神盾局的
He's an old colleague of my dad's, from S.H.I.E.L.D.
他们多年前就闹崩了
They had a falling out years ago.
你似乎经常跟人闹崩
You seem to have a lot of falling outs with people.
可能只是浪费时间
It's probably just a waste of time.
我光是在这里可就是赌上了一切
I'm risking everything by being here.
你不觉得我们该去问问吗
Don't you think we should check?
我们得查明是谁偷走了实验室
We need to find out who took the lab.
伙计们  这样暴露在外可不太好
Guys, it's not a good idea to be out in the open like this.
放松  没人会认出我们的
Relax, no one's gonna recognize us.
怎么  就因为帽子和墨镜吗
What, because of hats and sunglasses?
这不叫伪装  汉克
That's not a disguise, Hank.
我们只是像看棒球赛的自己
We look like ourselves at a baseball game.
在独立系统中
In an isolated system...
粒子以稳定相关系共存
particles co-exist in a stable phase relationship.
如果系统受到干扰
If the system is interfered with,
稳定就会变成混乱
that stability becomes chaos.
不可预测
Unpredictable.
危险  美妙
Dangerous. Beautiful.
完全独立的量子系统
Isolated completely, a quantum system
将退回到物质的分散状态
would revert back to separate states of matter...
每一个都与其环境的独特状态纠缠
each entangled with a distinct state of its environment.
也就是说
In other words,
这一物体将同时进出
the object in question would be both in and out of phase
多个平行现实的相
with multiple parallel realities.
说到跟现实不同步
Speaking of being out of phase with reality.
我注意到你们之中
I am noticing an unusually high number
有异常多的朦胧目光
of glazed eyes out there among you.
我们就提前几分钟结束吧
So, why don't we call it a few minutes early?
今天就到这儿吧
That'll be enough for today.
谢谢  女士们先生们  你们可以走了
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen, you may go.
真是难以置信  你与珍妮特相连
It's incredible. You're linked to Janet.
这是你脑中波斯纳分子的各量子态
It's quantum entanglement between the quantum states of
之间的量子纠缠
Posner molecules in your brains.
嗯  我也那么想的
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
你们是把"量子"一词加在每句话之前吗
Do you guys just put the word "quantum" in front of everything?
博士  我们得找到我们的实验室
Doctor, we need to find our lab.
霍普  我也想帮你
Hope, I'd love to help you...
但我并没有你说的那样的设备
but I don't have anything like the equipment you're describing.
我就说这是浪费时间  我们走吧
I told you this is a waste of time. Come on, let's go.
别瞧不起我  汉克
Don't condescend, Hank.
是你在躲避联调局的追捕
You're the one who's on the run from the FBI.
就因为你非得把自己放大到
All because you had to grow to a size
与你的自大相配的尺寸
that finally fit your ego.
德国那个不是我  是这个白痴
That wasn't me in Germany. It was this idiot.
真的
Really?
变那么大肯定很累吧
Going that big, it must've been exhausting.
我之后整整睡了三天  你都无法想象
I slept for three days straight. You have no idea.
我能想象
Actually, I do.
想当年  我曾跟汉克搭档搞过一个项目
Back in the day, I was Hank's partner on a project called
歌利亚[巨人]
Goliath.
等等  你是我的搭档吗
Excuse me? You were my partner?
唯一比变那么大还累的
The only thing more tiring than going that big
就是忍受汉克的臭脾气
is putting up with Hank's bullshit.
是啊
Right...
我不知道
I don't know.
你变得多大
How big did you get?
最高纪录是21英尺
My record? 21 feet.
-不赖啊  -你呢
- Not bad. - You?
算了
I don't...
不  真的  我很好奇
No, really, I'm curious.
65英尺  是啊
65 feet. Yeah.
-好大啊  -65英尺
- Huge. - 65.
如果你们俩比够大小了
If you two are finished comparing sizes...
我们得想办法追踪实验室
we need to figure out a way to track down the lab.
伟大的汉克·皮姆还没想到办法吗
And the great Hank Pym hasn't figured that one out yet?
奇怪啊
Strange.
你想当年可是无所不知
You had all the answers back in the day.
所以我才离开了项目
That's why I left the project.
离开吗
Left?
-是我炒了你  -我最正确的决定
- I fired you. - Best decision I ever made.
汉克是个糟糕的搭档  脾气暴躁
Hank was a terrible partner. Temperamental...
固执  没耐心
stubborn, impatient.
他迟早会把所有人都推开
Sooner or later, he just pushed everyone away.
只是那些庸才
Just the mediocrities.
珍妮特是唯一受得了他
Janet was the only one who could endure him
并选择留下来的
and chose to stick it out.
小心点  比尔
Watch it, Bill.
但她为此付出了代价  是吧
She paid the price, though, didn't she?
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
我不是来这儿听你俩吵嘴的
I didn't come here to listen to you two squabble.
我想救我妈妈
I'm trying to save my mother.
你说是哪个办公室
Now, which office would you say?
是吴
Oh, it's Woo.
肯定是有人看见了我
Someone must have seen me.
放松  如果是因为你
Relax. If this is about you,
他们早该赶到你家了
they'd be in your house by now.
你是15岁小孩吗
What are you, 15?
快点  我们得马上走了
Come on. We gotta go right now.
等等  你们或许能制造个临时追踪器
Wait. You might be able to improvise that tracker...
只需要修改你调节器的衍射组件
if you modify the diffraction units on one of your regulators.
-这可行  -我都不知道那是什么意思
- That could work. - I don't know what that means.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
但是  博士
But, Doctor,
校警说他们发现了皮姆和凡·戴恩
campus police says they ID'd both Pym and Van Dyne.
我不知道该怎么说  探员
I don't know what to tell you, Agent.
我都30年没跟汉克说过话了
I haven't talked to Hank in 30 years.
我向你保证
I can assure you
我是他最不会想见的人了
I'm the last person he would want to visit.
得了  你指望我们...
Oh, come on, you expect us to...
为什么
Why is that?
简单  我们恨死彼此了
Simple. We hate each other's guts.
我是糟糕的搭档
So I'm a terrible partner?
福斯特  在他平庸的职业生涯中
Foster, he hasn't had one good idea
就没想出过一个好点子
in his unremarkable career.
但他关于衍射器的点子可行  是吧
But his idea about the diffractors could work, right?
好吧  一个好点子
Fine, one decent idea.
但我升级战衣时
Except, I eliminated the diffractors
去掉了衍射器
when I upgraded the suits.
所以  如果我们有旧战衣
So, if we had an old suit,
我们或许就能追踪到实验室了
we might be able to track down the lab?
是的  但我们没有
Yes, but we don't.
-如果我们有呢  -你什么意思
- What if we did? - What do you mean?
我是说...
I mean...
人生很奇妙
life's funny.
天呐  你没销毁战衣
Oh, my God. You didn't destroy the suit.
什么
What?
那是你毕生的心血  汉克
Well, it was your life's work, Hank.
我不能销毁它
I couldn't destroy that.
我自首之前
Before I turned myself in,
我把它缩小然后邮给了路易斯
I shrunk it down and mailed it to Luis.
你把我的战衣邮寄了出去
You sent my suit through the mail?
邮政服务是非常可靠的
Hey, the postal service is very reliable.
现在有追踪码了  像快递服务一样
You know, they do tracking numbers now. Like UPS.
它在哪
Where is it?
在一个非常安全的地方  别担心
It's in a very safe place, all right? Don't worry.
奖杯吗  不在了
What, the trophy? No, it's not here.
什么叫不在了  还能在哪
What do you mean it's not there? Where could it be?
我到处看了  不在
I looked everywhere. It's not here.
别动那盆花
Hey, get away from the plant.
但我跟凯西玩过后  我放回...
But I put it back after Cassie and I...
展示说明
Show-and-tell.
斯科特
Scotty?
不  别
No, stop!
好消息是  我知道它在哪
Well, the good news is I know where it is.
布鲁克蒙特小学
不是说回到学校时
Whenever you go back to school
会觉得一切都变小了吗
isn't everything supposed to look so much smaller?
这地方看上去好大
This place seems huge.
怎么了
What is it?
是新调节器
It's the new regulator.
汉克  这件战衣怎么回事
Hank, what's going on with this suit?
到底是多"还没完成"
How much of a work in progress is this?
不不不
No, no, no.
你笑什么  拜托  你能不能
What are you, laughing? Please, could you just...
好啦
Okay, okay.
怎么样
What do you see?
尺寸线圈故障了
The sizing coils are malfunctioning.
让我...
Just let me...
-抱歉  -没事的
- Sorry. - It's all right.
好吧
Okay.
好了
All right.
现在试试
Try that.
抱歉
Sorry.
什么
What?
好啊
Awesome.
真希望美队现在能看到你
If only Cap could see you now.
好笑死了  我们怎么办
Hilarious. What are we gonna do?
你有通行证吗
Where's your hall pass?
我问你呢
Hey, I'm talking to you.
田中老师
布洛德韦尔老师
你可以的
You can do it.
马上够到了
You almost got it.
世界上最棒的奶奶
小花生
Oh, peanut.
好了  我们走
Okay, let's go.
好啊  哥们  今天在学校过得如何
Hiya, champ, how was school today?
好了  有笑话赶紧说完
All right, get your jokes out now.
能不能把战衣修好
Can you fix the suit?
脾气真坏
So cranky.
要不要来盒果汁和烤奶酪
You want a juice box and some string cheese?
你真有那个吗
Do you really have that?
看看福斯特说的对不对
Let's see if Foster was right.
检测到信号
这肯定是实验室了
This has gotta be the lab.
我们去拿吧
Let's go get it.
好
Yeah.
看上去是这里
This seems right.
看看我们  一天组队两次
Look at us, teaming up twice in one day.
真让人不禁想
Makes you think, huh?
想什么
About what?
德国
Germany.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们当时一起工作  一起训练
We were working together, training together...
还一起其他的
and other stuffing together.
如果我问了你  你会去吗
If I had asked you, would you have come?
看来我们永远不得而知了
I guess we'll never know.
但我知道一件事
But I do know one thing.
什么
What?
如果我去了  你就不会被抓了
If I had, you'd have never been caught.
斯科特
Scott.
你能不能暂时停止对我女儿做白日梦
You think you can stop daydreaming about my daughter
去把我的实验室拿回来
long enough to get my lab?
-是  先生  -谢谢
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
好了  信号收到
Okay, you're transmitting.
怎么这么慢
What took you so long?
抱歉  我给我的蚂蚁想名字来着
Sorry, I had to come up with a name for my ant.
我想叫他尤利西斯·格兰蚁
I'm thinking Ulysses S. Gr-Ant.
尤利西斯·格兰特是第18任美国总统
喜欢吗
You like it?
真好笑
Hilarious.
显示屏上什么都看不到
I'm not getting anything on the monitors.
有电子干扰
There's some kind of electronic disturbance.
你们小心
Be careful.
你知道我的  汉克  我一向小心
You know me, Hank. I'm always careful...
没事  只是那套衣服
It's okay. It's just the suit.
-你怎么知道  -看
- How do you know? - Look.
那是幽灵吗
That's Ghost?
她在干什么
What is she doing?
你觉得她是靠战衣
Do you think that suit
穿墙什么的吗
is how she goes through walls and stuff?
我们趁她还没醒赶紧走吧
Let's just get outta here before she wakes up.
霍普  看  实验室
Hope, look! There's the lab.
我们确定这是我们的缩小大楼
Now, we're sure this is our shrunken building
不是别人的吧
and not somebody else's, right?
快拿  斯科特  我们得动作快点
Just take it, Scott. Come on, we gotta be fast.
我拿
I'll get it.
该死
Oh, shit...
霍普  霍普  汉克
Hope. Hope! Hank.
伙计们
Guys.
他们应该听不到
I don't think they can hear you.
我是艾娃
I'm Ava.
斯科特
Scott.
看来
So,
你不需要战衣也能
you don't need the suit to ...
穿墙
go through things.
是啊
No.
它只是帮我控制这种状态
It just helps me control it.
本该也能抑制疼痛的
And the pain, supposedly.
你不会把手伸进我的胸膛
You're not gonna reach into my chest
捏爆我的心脏吧
and crush my heart, are you?
你真好玩
You're funny.
我不会伤害你的  斯科特  除非逼不得已
I'm not gonna hurt you, Scott, unless I have to.
我需要
I need...
你脑袋里的东西
what's in your head.
我们把其他人叫醒
Let's wake up the rest of the gang
赶紧开始吧  好吗
and get this over with, shall we?
醒醒
Get up!
醒过来
Come on!
爸爸
Dad?
你敢再碰他试试
Don't ever touch him again.
好了  霍普
Now, now, Hope...
我觉得考虑到一切
I think I'm being rather gentle with your father,
我对你父亲算温柔了
all things considered.
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
汉克·皮姆自大的另一个牺牲品
Another casualty of Hank Pym's ego.
比尔
Bill.
你做了什么
What have you done?
是你做了什么  皮姆博士
It's what you've done, Dr. Pym.
你跟她一起的
You're with her?
天呐  我以为你挺好呢
Oh, man. I thought you were cool.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
汉克估计没提过我父亲吧
I doubt Hank has ever mentioned my father.
他怎么会呢
Why would he?
埃利海斯·斯塔尔
Elihas Starr.
他们曾是神盾局的同事
They were colleagues at S.H.I.E.L.D.
量子研究
Quantum research.
直到我父亲胆敢反对伟大的汉克·皮姆
Until my father dare disagree with the great Hank Pym.
你让人开除了他
You had him fired.
还毁掉了他的名誉
Oh, and discredited for good measure.
我父亲想自己继续研究
My father tried to continue his research on his own.
为了恢复名誉  他不惜冒险
Desperate to restore his name, so he took risks.
不不
No, no, no!
太冒险了
Too many.
直到出了岔子
Until something went wrong.
他叫我们跑
He told us to run.
埃利海斯  怎么回事
Elihas, what's happening?
快跑吧  跑啊
Just go. Go!
爸爸  爸爸
Daddy! Daddy!
我看得出他很怕
I could tell he was scared.
爸爸
Daddy!
艾娃  不要
Ava, no!
我不想留下他一个人
I didn't want him to be alone.
不要啊
No! No!
不要
No!
我醒来时  我父母都死了
When I woke up, my parents were dead.
我就没那么幸运了
I wasn't so lucky.
他们称之为"分子失调"
They call it "molecular disequilibrium."
这名字挺蠢的
A rather dull name, I think.
并不能描述它的可怕
Doesn't quite do justice to what it means.
我身体里的每一个细胞都被撕碎
Every cell in my body is torn apart
然后又被组了回去
and stitched back together.
一遍又一遍
Over and over.
日复一日
Every day.
我当时还在神盾局  接到电话说
I was still at S.H.I.E.L.D. when I got the call about a
阿根廷发生了量子异常
quantum anomaly in Argentina.
你好  艾娃
Hello, Ava.
我叫比尔
My name's Bill.
我曾是你父亲的朋友
I was a friend of your father's.
我给你带了礼物
I brought you something.
没事  再试一次
It's all right. Try again.
这就对了
That's it.
福斯特博士尽力保护我了
Dr. Foster did his best to keep me safe.
但神盾局的其他人
But others at S.H.I.E.L.D.
把我的病症视为机会
saw an opportunity in my affliction.
他们给我造了件控制衣
They built me a containment suit,
让我控制变相
so I could control my phasing.
还训练我成为潜行特工
And trained me to be a stealth operative.
他们把我变成了武器
They weaponized me.
我为他们偷到  刺探
I stole for them. Spied for them.
杀戮
Killed for them.
我出卖灵魂的代价
And in exchange for my soul
是他们会治好我
they were going to cure me.
他们撒了谎
They lied.
神盾局陨落后  我收留了艾娃
When S.H.I.E.L.D. collapsed, I took Ava in.
我建造了这个舱来减缓她的衰退
I built the chamber to slow her decay,
但她的病情在加剧
but her condition was progressive.
我不知该如何治好她
I didn't know how to cure it.
她想杀你的  汉克  但我阻止了她
She wanted to kill you, Hank, but I told her no
而是叫她观察你
and that she should watch you instead.
不出所料
And sure enough,
她发现你在建隧道
she discovered that you were building the tunnel.
然后她又跟我讲了朗
Then, she told me about Lang.
以及珍妮特留在他脑袋里的信息
And the message from Janet inside his head,
于是我...
that's when I...
老天爷啊
Christ's sake!
是我的  抱歉
That's me. I'm sorry.
能告诉我是谁在给我发短信吗
Look, can you tell me who's texting me?
凯西  911
"Cassie, 911."
那是我女儿  我得给她回短信
That's my daughter. I need to text her back.
不  别想
No, that's not happening.
911就是紧急事件
What, it's 911. That means it's an emergency.
你没资格提要求  朗
You're not making demands here, Lang.
你不懂事态多么严...
You're not appreciating the gravity of the...
好吧  她在给我打视频电话了
Okay, look, she's trying to video chat me now.
可能真出事了  让我跟她说话  拜托了
Something might be wrong. Let me talk to her. Please.
凯西  你没事吧  什么急事
Cassie, are you okay? What's the emergency?
我找不到我的足球鞋了
I can't find my soccer shoes.
什么
What?
我明天还有比赛呢
I have a game tomorrow.
斯科特  我知道鞋就在那边
Hey, Scott, I know that they're there.
你能拿手机在家里走一圈吗
Can you just walk the phone around the house?
我现在不行啊
No, I can't do that right now.
-怎么了  -我病了
- Why not? - Because I'm sick.
你能不能稍后找找
Hey, can you just maybe look around later then
再打给我
and call me back?
拜托  谢谢
Please? Thank you.
再见  爸爸
Bye, Daddy!
-再见  小花生  -早日康复
- Bye, peanut! - Feel better!
早日康复  哥们
Feel better, buddy!
对不起  她说急事的
I'm sorry. It said emergency.
艾娃  我想帮你
Ava, I want to help you.
她不需要你的帮助  我知道怎么救她
She doesn't need your help. I know how to save her.
是吗  怎么救
Oh, really? How?
珍妮特
Janet.
她这30年来
For the last 30 years,
都在量子域吸收量子能
she's been down there absorbing quantum energy.
我们可以提取那能量
We can extract that energy.
用它来修复艾娃的分子结构
We can use it to repair Ava's molecular structure...
提取
Extract it?
-是的  -你疯了吗
- Yes. - Are you insane?
那会把珍妮特撕裂的
That would rip Janet apart.
这你不能确定
You don't know that.
我要开启隧道
I'm gonna fire up your tunnel.
等珍妮特的位置出现在朗脑子里
When Janet's location pops into Lang's head,
他就得告诉我
he's gonna give it to me
否则我就把他交给联调局
or I'm gonna turn him over to the FBI.
什么
What?
你给我留在这里
You are gonna stay here
以防我需要你帮忙
just in case I need your help.
我才不会帮你
Like hell I would help you!
我怎么说你就得怎么做
You'll do whatever I say.
你会害死珍妮特的
You're gonna kill Janet!
你还是多担心自己吧  汉克
I'd be more worried about yourself, Hank.
该死  比尔
Goddamn it, Bill!
-爸爸  -冷静  汉克
- Dad? - Calm down, Hank.
老天啊
So help me God...
药
The pills.
他的心脏  他需要吃药
It's his heart! He needs his pills.
求你  福斯特博士
Please, Dr. Foster.
药就在铁盒里  拜托了
They're in the tin. Please.
他会死的  拜托
He could die! Come on!
帮他啊
Help him!
爸爸  撑住了
Dad, just hang on, all right?
继续呼吸  冷静点
Just keep breathing. Stay calm.
帮他啊  快点
Help him, man! Come on!
那个薄荷糖盒
The Altoid tin!
等等
Wait!
谢谢了  伙计们
Thanks, guys.
汉克
Hank!
比尔给那姑娘灌输了一脑子的谎言
Bill is filling that girl's head with lies.
埃利海斯·斯塔尔是个叛徒
Elihas Starr was a traitor.
他偷了我的图纸
He stole my plans.
往下点  锁定
Now, bring it down. All right, lock it in.
不不  螺栓在另一边
No, no, no. The bolt is on the other side.
把那个锁紧  往下拉一点
Tighten that one down, then bring it down one notch.
好样的
Good job.
会成功的
It'll work.
福斯特  要是他做  会烧毁系统的
Foster, he could have fried the entire system.
我们调整继电器
Look, we'll adjust the relays
你去重编程设置
while you go reprogram the settings, all right?
会成功的
It's going to be fine.
关键时刻到了
So, this is it.
是啊  按说筹备了这么久
Yeah. You'd think with all this time to prepare
我该准备好了
I'd be more ready.
你是没法为进入亚原子状态做好准备的
Oh, going subatomic isn't something you can prepare for.
那会模糊你的意识
It kind of melts your mind.
我是指再见到我妈妈
I mean seeing my mom again.
如果她完全变成了另一个人呢
What if she's a completely different person?
是啊  比如变成了乔治·华盛顿
Yeah, like, uh, George Washington.
我说真的  斯科特
I'm serious, Scott.
或是乔治·杰斐逊
Or George Jefferson.
如果她已经忘记了我呢
What if she's forgotten about me?
我在监狱时
When I was in prison...
唯一帮我度过那段时光的就是凯西
the only thing that got me through was Cassie.
我哪怕被关个100年
I could have been locked up for 100 years...
也绝不会忘记她
I never would have forgotten her.
我知道你妈妈肯定在数着
I know your mom is counting the minutes
与你分开的每一分钟
until she can see you again.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们有大麻烦了
We got a big problem.
你忘记大楼后面的
You forgot the motion sensor lights
运动传感器灯了
on the back of the building.
糟糕
Oh, no.
提议案里有
And they're on the proposal,
卡拉佩特安还特地问到了
and Karapetyan asked for them specifically.
是啊  我们忙得挺疯的
Uh, yeah, look, it's been a little crazy.
这样吧  我明天过去  看一眼
Look, maybe I could stop by tomorrow, take a look at it.
不行
No. No, no, no, no.
明天一大早就要见面了
The meeting is first thing in the morning.
你得马上过来解决它
You gotta come right now and fix it.
我不能  我也想  但我不能走
I can't. I wish I could, but I can't leave.
这样  我去找你
You know what, I'm coming to you.
我带图纸过去  就在笔记本电脑上
I'll just bring the plans. They're on the laptop.
你在那里修改
And you can fix them there.
告诉我你在哪里
Just tell me where you are, okay?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
什么意思  一言难尽
What do you mean it's complicated?
如您所见  先生
As you can see, sir,
这套系统是最先进的
this system is state of the art.
明日的安保系统  今日享用
Security of tomorrow, today.
太棒了
Oh, that's so good!
我喜欢你的探身  继续练习
And I love the lean-in, bro. Keep practicin'.
我得开车去斯科特那里
Hey, I just gotta drive up to Scotty's,
我们好修改图纸
so we can fix the plans.
别担心  我回来时肯定还有时间
But don't worry, I'll be back in plenty of time.
如您所见
As you can see...
你们为明早把货车洗干净了吧
Tell me you got the van washed for tomorrow morning.
地盘都洗了
Down to the undercarriage, baby.
你还要了洗地盘
You sprung for the undercarriage wash?
你叫我全洗的
Well, you said get the works.
那是骗人的  哥们
That's a scam, bro.
我们住在加州  又不是明尼苏达州
We live in California, not Minnesota.
他说得对
He's right.
洗底盘
The undercarriage wash,
是为了洗掉除冰盐
that's for cleaning off road salt
我们更爱下雪的姐妹州的道路上才会撒那个
laid down in our more snow-laden sister states.
你是谁  你怎么会这么清楚洗车行业的规矩
Who are you, and why do you know so much about car wash protocol?
我叫桑尼·伯奇
Well, my name is Sonny Burch.
我很会做调查  路易斯
And I do my research, Luis.
我还从一个联调局的朋友那里得知
To wit, I have learned from a friend of mine at the FBI
你跟斯科特·朗相熟
that you are a known associate of Scott Lang...
斯科特和汉克·皮姆相熟  我还知道
a known associate of Hank Pym, who I've also learned
汉克有个便携式可缩小实验室
has a portable shrinking laboratory
里面有各式各样有趣的科技
filled with all kinds of juicy tech.
你得告诉我  它在哪
And you're gonna tell me where it is.
我真不想告诉你
Well, I hate to break it to you, but
但我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你好像有点抵触  路易斯
Well, I sense a resistance in you, Luis.
但我答应了某些危险人物给他们问出结果
And I have promised results to some dangerous people.
所以  给你介绍一下我的好友  乌兹曼
So, I'm gonna introduce you to my good friend, Uzman.
乌兹曼特别擅长
Now... Uzman is a master
通过精神手段
at extracting information
撬开不愿开口的人的嘴
from the unwilling through psychoactive means.
那是吐真剂吗
Oh, is that truth serum?
不存在吐真剂这种东西
There's no such thing as truth serum.
那就是电视节目的鬼扯
That's just nonsense from TV.
那它是什么
Well, what is it then?
这是一种混合药剂
It's a little concoction
从他当年还在MI6时  他就一直在改良
that he's been perfecting since his days with the S.I.S.
它会让你极容易受到暗示  有问必答
It makes you suggestible and highly responsive.
哥们  那就是吐真剂
Well, dude, that's truth serum.
不是的
No, it's not.
无意冒犯  但是我觉得那就是吐真剂
No offensing, but they sound like truth serum to me.
-是吧  -它不是吐真剂
- Right? - It's not a truth serum.
好吧  我相信你
Okay. Hey, I believe you.
不是吐真剂
It's not a truth serum.
如果它看起来像吐真剂  功能也是吐真
I mean, if it walk like duck and talk like ducks...
那它就是吐真剂
The truth serum.
我过敏的东西可多了
Well, I have a lot of allergies...
请你三思
so you might wanna think about that.
我们得夺回实验室
We've got to get that lab back.
怎么了
What?
舱和战衣几乎无法帮你控制病情了
The chamber and the suit are barely helping anymore.
我还能活多久
How long have I got?
几周吧
A couple of weeks, maybe.
那我们逼他们把实验室拿回来
Well, then we'll make them bring the lab back.
怎么做
How?
朗  他有个女儿  对吧
Lang. He has a daughter, right?
你不是真想这么干吧
You can't mean that.
艾娃
Ava!
你在外面惹的祸  我都忍了
I tolerate a lot of the things you do out there...
但这种事我绝不参与
but I won't be a part of anything like that.
在渐渐消失的不是你  比尔
You're not the one who's about to fade away into nothing, Bill.
而是我
I am!
你说你能治好我
You said you could fix me!
你保证过的
You promised.
我知道  我会的
I know. I will.
但不能那样做
But not like that.
你敢碰那小女孩一下
You lay one finger on that little girl...
我就不帮你了  我俩就到此为止
I won't help you. And we're done.
好吧
Fine.
还有其他选择
There are other options.
你知道吗  你说得对  这不是吐真剂
You know what? You're right. This isn't truth serum.
因为我一点感觉都没有
Because I don't feel anything.
我撒谎了  我有感觉
That was a lie. I do feel something.
这就是吐真剂
This is truth serum!
吐真剂是不存在的
There's no such thing!
好了
Okay.
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
很简单  路易斯
Now, I'm gonna make this real easy for you, Luis.
好
Okay.
斯科特·朗在哪
Where is Scott Lang?
这事说来话长
Well, see, that's complicated.
我第一次遇见斯科特时  他糟透了
Because when I first met Scotty, he was in a bad place.
而且我不是指牢房D区
And I'm not talkin' about cell block D.
他妻子刚刚申请离婚  我说
His wife had just filed for divorce, and I was, like...
"该死  哥们  她在你蹲号子时甩了你"
"Damn, homie. She dumped you when you're on lockup?"
他说"是啊  我知道
And he was, like, "Yeah, I know.
我以为我能跟她白头偕老呢
"I thought I was gonna be with her forever...
结果现在我孤身一人"
"But now I'm all alone."
我说"哥们  你知道吗
And I was, like, "Damn, homie. You know what?
振作点  你有新搭档了
"You gotta chin up, because you'll find a new partner.
你知道吗  我是路易斯"
"But you know what? I'm Luis."
他说"你知道吗  我是斯科特
And he says, "You know what? I'm Scotty,
我们会成为铁哥们的"
"And we're gonna be best friends."
打住  打住
Okay, hold on, hold on.
我很喜欢听精彩的故事
I like a good story as much as the next person...
但是  这些跟斯科特·朗在哪
but what in the hell does this have to do
有什么关系
with where Scott Lang is?
我快讲到了  就快讲到了
I'm getting there. I'm getting there.
你投了币  就得听完整首歌
You put a dime in him, you gotta let the whole song play out.
他就像人形点唱机
He like human jukebox.
我奶奶开的餐厅里有台点唱机
Oh, my abuelita had a jukebox in the restaurant!
是啊  只放莫里西的歌
Yeah, only played Morrissey.
要是有人抱怨  她就...
And if anybody ever complained, she'd be like...
墨西哥裔  我们喊他们墨兹
You know, Chicanos, we call him "Moz."
然后她就说"不送"
Then, ¡adios!
没办法  他忧郁的情歌让我们很有共鸣
What can I say? We relate to his melancholy ballads, you know?
-朗  -好好好
- Lang! - Right, right, right.
后来  斯科特出狱了
So, anyway, Scotty gets out of jail,
他开始为汉克工作
and he starts working for Hank.
这时他遇到了霍普  霍普却一副
That's when he met Hope. And Hope's all, like...
"我不想跟你扯上关系
"I want nothing to do with you.
看看我的发型  我超正经"的样子
"Look at my hairdo, I'm all business."
斯科特就说
And then Scotty's, like,
知道吗  妹子  我的心已碎
"You know what, girl? My heart is all broken.
我可能再也不会爱了
"And I'll probably never find love again,
但我可真想吻你
"But damn if I want to kiss you!"
时间快进
But then you fast forward
他们就爱上彼此了
and they're all into each other, right?
然后斯科特说
And then Scotty's, like,
知道吗  我不能告诉你
"You know what? I can't tell you this...
但我要去跟美国队长砸烂一座机场
"But I'm gonna go trash an airport with Captain America."
然后她说  真不敢相信你就那么跑了
And then she said, "I can't believe you split like that!
回见了  蠢蛋
"Smell you later, dummy."
于是斯科特就被软禁了
So, Scotty goes on house arrest.
他不肯承认  但他心里觉得
And he won't admit it, but his heart is all, like...
该死  我还以为霍普可以成为
"Damn! I thought Hope coulda been
我的新真搭档呢  但我搞砸了
"My new true partner, but I blew it!"
但命运让他们又走到了一起
But fate brought 'em back together.
然后霍普心里就想
And then Hope's heart is all...
我担心我不能信任他
"I'm worried that I can't trust him...
他会再次搞砸  毁掉一切
"And he's gonna screw up again, and ruin everything!"
然后我心里就想
And then my heart is all, like...
那高档覆盆子点心代表了公司的负债
"That fancy raspberry filling represents the company's red
我们只差几天就要倒闭了
"And we're days away from going out of business. "
倒闭
"Out of business"?
只差几天
"Days away"?
该死的吐真剂
Damn truth serum!
我其实是想保护你们的  我发誓
I was trying to protect you guys. I swear to God.
我是想做个好老板的  但我们破产了
I was trying to be a good boss, but we're broke!
卡拉佩特安是我们的最后希望
And the Karapetyan's our last hope.
如果我们不去  我们就完了
And if we don't show up, we're done!
这叫什么好老板
That's terrible bossing!
该死  哥们
Damn, bro!
这怪我  这怪我
That's on me! That's on me!
够了
Enough.
我要再问你一次
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
斯科特·朗在哪
Where is Scott Lang?
我这不说呢吗
I've been trying to tell you,
他现在处境尴尬  从情感上说
he's in a tricky spot, emotionally speaking.
从情感上说
Emotionally speaking.
那斯科特·朗  人在哪里
Well, where is Scott Lang, literally speaking!
森林里
The woods.
The woods?
雅加婆婆
Baba Yaga!
什么意思  "森林里"
What do you mean, "The woods"?
缪尔森林
The Muir Woods,
全景高速的第二条消防道路上
the second fire road off the Panoramic Highway!
老天爷啊
For God's sake!
雅加婆婆  晚上到来
Baba Yaga, come at night
小娃娃们  好好睡
Little children, sleepy tight
该死的
Damn it!
如果那怪物拿到皮姆的设备
If that freak gets Pym's tech...
我就再别想找回来了
I'm never gonna see it.
我们怎么办
So, what do we do now?
从联调局那里偷
It's easier to steal it from the Feds
比从妖怪那里偷要简单
than from the boogeyman.
是我  你想升个职吗
Hey, it's me. How'd you like to get a promotion?
我知道皮姆  凡·戴恩和朗在哪
I got the location on Pym, Van Dyne and Lang.
但你得马上去抓到他们
But you gonna have to take 'em down now,
因为他们不会在那里待很久的
because they ain't gonna be there for long.
等你抓到他们  你要把实验室给我
And when you do, you gonna get me that lab.
知道了
Understood.
好消息  先生们
Good news, gentlemen.
联调局会替我们完成累活儿
Feds are gonna do the hard work for us.
看什么呢  替我换胎
What are you lookin' at? Change my tires!
好
Right.
线上近景魔术大学
-先生  -不知道敲门吗
- Sir. - Can you knock?
抱歉  先生  我收到条线索
Sorry, sir. Uh, but I just got a lead.
我喜欢线索
I love leads.
系统已就绪
System's in the green.
线圈充电
Priming the coils.
满电
Full charge.
等隧道打开
As soon as the tunnel's open
一旦你收到任何疑似是
let us know if you get anything
她的信息  都告诉我们
that could be a part of her message.
好的  没问题
Yeah, yeah. I will.
那好
Okay, then.
开始了
Here it goes.
我们成功了
We did it!
有反应吗
You got anything?
没有
Nothin'.
等一等  因为可能...
Well, just give it a minute, because it could...
不
No.
不不不
No, no, no, no!
怎么回事
What's happening?
要停机了  可能是我们的向量不对
It's shutting down. Maybe our vectors are off.
我们都算过一百万次了  肯定是对的
We've gone over them a million times, I know they're right!
那还能是因为什么
Then what else could it be?
我不知道
I don't know!
-斯科特  你干吗  -斯科特  别乱动
- Scott, what are you doing? - Scott, get away from that!
斯科特  你别...
Scott, you can't...
对不起  我不知道我还有多久
I'm sorry, I don't know how much time I have.
我得改好算法
I need to fix the algorithm.
相信我  在下面待了30年
Trust me, after 30 years down here...
我都想得很清楚了
I've thought about it a lot.
珍妮特
Janet?
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
小糖豆
Jellybean.
妈妈
Mom?
这并不是我所想象的团聚
It's not the reunion I'd imagined.
太赶了
It's all so rushed.
你俩做得太棒了
You two have done such great work.
你们只需要一点点的
You just need a little...
帮助
nudge.
珍妮特  这怎么可能
Janet, how is this possible?
你放在斯科特脑子里的不是一则信息
It wasn't a message you put in Scott's head.
而是个天线
It was an antenna.
真聪明
Clever girl.
我好为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
亲爱的  告诉我们你在哪
Honey, tell us where you are.
告诉我们怎么找到你
Tell us how to find you.
不  概率场太复杂了
No, the probability fields are too complex.
所以我才需要跟你对话
That's why I needed to talk to you.
你得追随我的声音
You have to follow my voice.
当然了
Of course!
就像追踪一同电话
Like tracing a call back to its source!
我在用亚原子频率追踪你的信号
I'm tracking your signal using subatomic frequencies
范围是1点和9点
between point two and point nine.
最好缩小到4和6
I'd narrow it to four and six.
太窄了  可能会错过你
That's too tight. We could miss you.
看看我们  又在吵了
Look at us squabbling again.
好吧  那就3和7
Fine. All right, between three and seven.
我们数十年来第一次吵架  就这么结束了
Our first fight in decades, and it's over just like that.
正中红心
Bullseye.
信号源锁定
Source lock.
是你
It's you.
我们找到了
We got it!
你们得去这个坐标找我
You have to meet me at these exact coordinates.
在荒原里  越过量子虚无
In the wasteland, beyond the quantum void.
那里很危险
It's very dangerous,
尤其是对人类大脑  务必小心
especially on the human mind, so be careful.
时间和时空的规则在这里很不一样
Time and space work very differently down here.
你们只有两小时
You have two hours.
之后  概率场会变动
After that, the probability fields will shift...
要再过一世纪
and it'll be another century
才能再次这样对齐了
before they align like this again.
我们会找到你的
We'll find you.
我知道你会的  小糖豆
I know you will, Jellybean.
不
Nope.
没感觉  我完全没感觉
Nothing. I got nothing.
完全感觉不到珍妮特
No sign of Janet.
这可好
Perfect.
我们怎么上来的
How did we get up here?
好  首先你会看到好多光
All right, first you're gonna see all kinds of lights...
然后会变得很颠簸
and it's gonna get really trippy...
然后会一片漆黑寂静  非常寂静
but then it's gonna turn black and silent. Really silent.
斯科特  我没事的
Scott, I'll be fine.
我就是说说  因为我去过嘛
I'm just saying because I've been down there.
嗯  你说过了
Yeah, so you've mentioned.
抱歉  我得接一下
Um, sorry. I have to take this.
哥们  你来不来啊
Hey, man, you coming?
我不去了  但知道吗  幽灵要去
No, I'm not, but you know what? Ghost is.
知道吗  联调局  他们也知道你们在哪
And you know what? The Feds, they know where you are.
-什么  -对不起
- What? - I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
他们给我用了吐真剂
They gave me some truth serum.
然后我突然就开始老实交待
And then all of a sudden I started talkin' all honestly.
比如  我讨厌你用洗碗机的方式
Like, I hate the way that you load the dishwasher.
我非常讨厌
I hate it, I hate it.
但你得回家了
But you need to go home
因为联调局可能正在赶过去
because the Feds are probably going there now!
对了
And by the way...
谁会把盘子放在最上层啊  就不该放那里
who puts the plates on the top rack? They don't go there!
我觉得自己好混蛋
I feel like such a jerk.
你们会气死的  我们得马上走了
You're gonna be really mad. We gotta go now.
什么
What?
幽灵和联调局都知道我们在哪了
Ghost knows where we are. So does the FBI.
怎么会
How?
-我告诉路易斯了  -什么
- I told Luis where we are. - You what?
我叫他过来
I told him to come here
我好帮忙修改卡拉佩特安的提议案
so I could help him with the Karapetyan proposal.
天呐
Oh, my God!
听着  我们必须拿到那个客户
Look, we need to land that account.
否则我们会失业的
Otherwise, we lose the business!
你们知道前科犯现在找工作多难吗
Do you know hard it is for ex-cons to find work these days?
天呐  斯科特
Jesus, Scott!
关闭孔洞需要90秒
90 seconds to close the aperture!
我们得先给线圈消磁
You have to depolarize the coils first!
我知道
I know!
我很抱歉  但是
I'm really sorry, but the, um...
联调局要去我家了
FBI is coming to my place so...
我得走了
I have to go.
我能借用下战衣吗
Can I borrow the suit?
回转仪稳定器
Gyroscopic stabilizers.
启动
Powering on.
我要把战衣借走了
I'm just gonna borrow the suit.
我会回来的  告诉我你们会去哪
I'll come back. Just tell me where you'll be.
-不必了  -什么
- Don't bother. - What?
我们找到我妈妈后
We'll come and get the suit from you,
会去找你取回战衣的
as soon as we've found my mom.
-霍普  -斯科特  走吧
- Hope... - Scott, just go!
-斯科特  -爸爸
- Scott? - Daddy?
是我们  哥们
It's us, buddy!
我们来拿凯西的鞋
We're here for Cassie's shoes!
他肯定在休养
He must be resting.
亲爱的  你上楼去你床底下找找吧
Honey, why don't you go upstairs and look under your bed?
爸爸  你在楼上吗
Daddy, you upstairs?
爸爸
Daddy?
怎么...
What the...
他现在真是脏得像猪
He really lives like a pig these days.
爸爸
Daddy?
散开
Spread out!
又来
Again?
你们真不知耻
You people have no shame!
监控器显示他在浴室
The monitor says that he's in the bathroom.
我才不信
Yeah, I'm not buying it!
凯西  让他过去
Cassie, let the man get by!
但爸爸病得好厉害
But Daddy's super sick!
我去瞧瞧看
I'll see about that!
他说他不希望传染别人
He says he doesn't want anyone else to get sick!
我乐意冒个险  亲爱的
Well, I'll take my chances, sweetie.
他吐了  好多呢
He barfed. Like, a lot.
小姑娘  我是联邦探员
Young lady, I'm a federal agent.
我见过比呕吐物更糟的东西
I've seen worse things than vomit.
好多好多吗
Like, "a lot" a lot?
-是啊  -不管了  让开
- Yes! - Forget it, move aside!
不要
No!
-你怎么来了  -斯科特
- What are you doing here? - Scott.
抱歉  我病得很重
I'm sorry, I'm just really sick.
我说了吧
I told you.
抱歉
Excuse me.
有时就必须得吐出来  是吧
Sometimes you gotta just get it out. You know?
抱歉
Sorry.
我去启动车
I'll start the van.
你拿实验室
You get the lab.
别动  你们被包围了
Freeze! You're surrounded!
汉克·皮姆
Hank Pym...
霍普·凡·戴恩
Hope Van Dyne...
你们被捕了
you're under arrest.
诊断无问题
这是骚扰
This is harassment!
其实  不是的
Actually, it's not.
联调局什么意思啊
What does the FBI even stand for...
永远骚扰个人吗
"Forever Bothering Individuals"?
-他的监控器没问题吗  -当然了
- His monitor check out? - Of course it does.
该死
Damn it!
看来我被骗了
Looks like I just got fed a bowl of malarkey.
我们抓到他们了  先生
We got 'em, sir.
皮姆和凡·戴恩都已被羁押
Pym and Van Dyne are in custody.
真的吗  太好了
Seriously? Yes!
抱歉  斯科特
Oh, I'm sorry, Scott.
他们是你的朋友  这太不体谅了
They're your friends. That's insensitive.
我太需要赢一局了
I just really needed a win, you know?
好了  我会稍后回来
Anyway, I'll be back later
正式结束你的刑期
for the official end of your sentence!
抱歉看错你了  哥们
Sorry for misjudging you, pal!
你该为自己感到骄傲
You should feel great about yourself!
-怎么了  -有人受伤
- What is it? - We have a man down.
皮姆的实验室不见了
And Pym's lab is gone.
谢谢你掩护我
Thanks for covering for me.
不客气
Sure.
那么
So...
你又开始做蚁人多久了
how long have you been Ant-Man again?
没多久
Not long.
就那么发生了
It just sort of happened.
很抱歉我隐瞒了你
I'm sorry for lying to you...
很抱歉我赌上了一切
and I'm sorry for risking everything.
爸爸  没事的
Daddy, it's okay.
不是没事
It's not.
我做了些蠢事
I do some dumb things...
而我最爱的人却为此付出代价
and the people that I love the most pay the price.
主要是你
Mainly you.
帮助他人不是蠢事
Trying to help people isn't dumb.
但我几乎每次都搞砸了
I screw it up just about every time.
或许你是需要有人照应你
So, maybe you just need someone watching your back,
比如找个搭档
like a partner.
她说得很清楚  那是她最不想做的事了
Well, she's made it clear that's about the last thing she wants.
谁
Who?
霍普
Hope.
等等  你想的是谁
Wait, who did you think?
我
Me.
你吗
You?
别笑
Don't laugh.
我能做个好搭档的
I'd be a great partner.
小花生
Aw, peanut.
你肯定可棒了
You would be awesome.
但如果我允许你做
And if I let you...
我就是个坏爸爸了
I would be a terrible dad.
好吧
Fine.
那就让霍普做你的搭档吧  她挺聪明的
Then have Hope be your partner. She's smart.
她让我想到了你
She reminds me of you.
你要去帮她吗
You gonna go help her?
我觉得你该帮她
I think you should help her.
我也希望我能
I wish I could, but...
但我不知道我要怎么帮她而不伤害到你
I don't know how I could help her without hurting you.
你可以的
You can do it.
你什么都可以做到
You can do anything.
你是世界上最棒的奶奶
You are the world's greatest grandma.
吴探员一小时来见你们
Agent Woo will see you in an hour.
一小时  我们没有那么多时间
An hour? We don't have an hour.
你们有别处要去吗
You got somewhere else to be?
这才是我的好闺女
Oh, now, that's my girl.
好了  我们的计划是什么
All right, what's our plan?
缩小那面墙
To shrink that wall.
看上去像是承重墙
It looks load-bearing.
天花板可能会塌的
The ceiling could collapse.
那我们就没命跑
Then we run like hell.
我估计这一层有15到20个探员
Now, I estimate 15-20 agents on the floor.
楼里大概还有五倍这个数的探员
Roughly five times that in the building at large.
他们都有武器
They're all heavily armed.
胜算不高
Not great odds.
你有更好的主意吗
You got any better ideas?
没有
Nope.
我不会放弃妈妈的
And I'm not giving up on Mom.
她肯定会为你骄傲的
She'd be so proud of you.
好了
Okay.
一
One...
二
two...
斯科特
Scott?
你俩傻站着干什么
What're you two just standing around for?
我们得去找到实验室
We gotta go find that lab.
那我呢
What about me?
好啊
Perfect.
快换衣服  我们没多少时间
Hurry up and get dressed. We don't have much time.
先生
Sir.
现在呢
Okay, now what?
你问我吗
You're asking me?
进来
Get in!
打扰  我们打算赶紧离开吗
Excuse me. Are we planning on leaving soon
还是你俩要继续互相凝视
or are you two gonna keep staring at each other
直到他们开始冲我们开火
until they start shooting at us?
好吧
Yeah.
-伯奇  -嗯
- Hey, Burch. - Yeah.
他们出来了
Yeah, they're out.
我就来
I'm on my way.
她的战衣不见了  车也是
Her suit is missing, and so is the van.
怎么会这样
How could this happen?
怎么回事啊
I mean, what the dickens?
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我们怎么找到实验室
So, uh, how do we find the lab?
丢过一次后
After we lost it the first time
我放了新的追踪器
I put on a new tracker
算是吧
of sorts.
这也行
That'll work.
好没好啊
Is it ready or not?
我们可以开始进行提取了
We can begin the extraction process.
听着  艾娃
Listen, Ava.
这整件事可能会很危险
This whole thing could be very dangerous.
或许我们该
Maybe we should...
或许我们该什么  等吗
Maybe we should what? Wait?
我只能再活几天了
I've got days until I'm dead.
我们要做了  比尔
We're doing this, Bill.
马上
Now.
能量读数显示他们还没用过隧道
Energy readings show they have not used the tunnel yet.
我们没多少时间了
We don't have much time
妈妈的位置就要变化  我们就会失去她
before Mom's location shifts, and we lose her.
好  那之前还有好多事呢
Yeah, and we have a lot to do before then.
我爸爸总说
You know, my pep-pep always said,
如果你想做好什么事  就列个单子
"If you want to do something right, you make a list."
我们该那么做
So, we should do that.
一  我们要闯入实验室
One, we have to break into that lab.
二  我们要赶走福斯特和幽灵
Two, we have to kick out Foster and Ghost.
三  我们得跟幽灵打
Three, we're gonna have to fight Ghost.
这似乎该是二的一部分  二A吧
That seems like it should be part of two. 2-A, all right?
就算是二A吧
Let's call it 2-A.
打幽灵  二A
Fight Ghost. 2-A.
还有  我们得确保实验室恢复到原始大小
Also, we have to make sure that the lab is fully grown
好让你出来
for you to come back.
否则我们就完了
Otherwise, we're screwed.
斯科特
Scott!
要我再说一次吗  我再说一次
You want me to start again? I'll start again...
我去
I'm going to dive.
我们要想成功  就得你俩在外面
The only chance we got is if the two of you are out here...
一起保护隧道
together, protecting the tunnel.
让我去吧  霍普  求你
Let me do this, Hope. Please.
让我去接她
Let me get her.
我觉得他是对的
I think he's right.
好啊
"Whassup?"
不记得那个特火的广告吗
You don't remember, uh, that beloved commercial?
"好啊"
"Whassup?"
我让他跟我们过来的
I had him follow us.
我觉得我们会需要帮助
I thought we could use some help.
好了  我就位了
All right. I'm in position.
蚂蚁过去了
The ants are headed in.
收到
Copy that.
眼睛放亮了  斯科特
Keep your eyes peeled, Scotty.
-来点糖吗  -不
- Do you want Pez? - No.
我生日时凯西给我的
Cassie gave me this for my birthday.
对了  我爱那套战衣
By the way, I love that suit!
谢谢
Thanks, man.
真希望我也有一套
I wish I had a suit.
就算是没多少能力的我也会喜欢的
I would even like a suit with minimal powers, you know?
或者就是一件没任何能力的战衣
Or maybe even just a suit, with no powers.
怎么回事
What is it?
不知道
Don't know.
是他们
It's them!
他们肯定就在附近
They can't be far.
汉克  汉克
All right, Hank. Hank?
爸爸  你什么情况
Dad, what's your status?
福斯特已经解决了
Foster's taken care of.
这就换战衣
Suiting up now.
我只是想救艾娃
I just wanted to save Ava.
她要面临死亡或更恐怖的命运
She's facing death or something far more terrible.
她害怕
She's afraid.
等我回来时  会帮你想办法的
I'll help you find a cure when I get back.
我保证
I promise.
我们会一起想出个办法来的
Together, we'll figure something out.
祝你好运  汉克
Good luck, Hank.
谢谢  比尔
Thanks, Bill.
现在我需要你退后
Now, I'm gonna need you to step back.
剩余时间  15分钟
Time remaining, 15 minutes.
汉克进去了  斯科特
Hank's in, Scott.
看到她了吗
Any sign of her?
没有  还没有
No, nothing yet.
艾娃
Ava!
让蚂蚁走开  斯科特
Call off the ants, Scott.
该死
Oh, boy!
报告下情况
Can I get a status report?
我这里在正面遭遇幽灵
'Cause I got some serious Ghost problems here!
准备进入
Ready to dive.
-如果我回不来  -别
- In case I don't make it... - Don't.
别那么说
Don't say that.
我不能也失去你
I can't lose you, too.
我爱你  霍普
I love you, Hope.
伙计们  这里情况很糟
Guys, everything's bad over here.
动手
Now.
误导
Misdirection.
线上近景魔术大学的
One of the first things they teach you
第一课
at Online Close-up Magic University.
不
No!
计划成功了  我们拿到了  斯科特
Plan worked. We got it, Scotty!
去汇合点见
Meet us at the rendezvous point.
好的  我就去
Okay, on my way!
不
Oh, no.
不是吧  又是这人
Really? This guy again?
谁
Who?
我就说我们还没完事呢
I told you our business wasn't over.
计划有变
Change of plans.
坐稳
Hang on.
我要那个实验室  不惜一切
I want that lab, boys, whatever it takes.
抓稳
Hold on.
底盘脏死了
That undercarriage is filthy!
他们有更大的问题呢
They got bigger problems.
霍普  你干什么呢
Hope, what're you doing?
你在远离汇合点
You're heading away from the rendezvous point!
别担心
Don't worry,
我要带他们去看风景
I'm taking these guys on the scenic route.
什么意思
Wait, what're you...
天呐  天呐  我们要死了
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! We're gonna die!
我们要死了
We're gonna die!
信号丢失
Signal lost.
他们在上面干什么呢
What the hell are they doing up there?
重新校准
Recalibrating.
你可没说过这里这么美  斯科特
You never said it was so beautiful, Scott.
重新校准
Recalibrating.
好了  快点吧
Okay, any time now.
重新校准
Recalibrating.
-重新校准  -快啊
- Recalibrating. - Come on.
信号恢复
Signal restored.
机车  你们上
Bikes, it's all you.
-你来开  -什么  等等
- Take the wheel. - What? Wait!
60年代玩得爽  现在苦果来了
Well, the 60's were fun, but now I'm paying for it.
你小心点
Be careful up there!
饶了我吧   我两年没开车了
Give me a break! I haven't driven in two years!
你被糖果盒砸了
You got pezed!
过来
Up here!
那可不妙
Oh, that's not good.
霍普
Hope!
-不  -不
- No! No! - No!
在那里呢  去抢实验室
There it is, right there. Get the lab!
去抢啊
Get the lab!
我看到她了  弗里蒙特街向西
I've got her. Westbound on Fremont.
霍普  等我
Hope! Wait!
我怎么办
What about me?
我们抓到你了  艾娃
We got you now, Ava!
别又来
Not again!
垃圾玩意
Piece of junk!
太好了
Yes!
走走走
Go, go, go, go, go!
伯奇拿到了实验室
Burch got the lab.
我去追他
I'm going after him.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no!
还没完成个屁
Work in progress, my ass...
斯科特  你在哪
Scott, where are you?
我看到伯奇了  快来
I've got Burch in my sights. Hurry!
我来了  我来了
I'm coming, I'm coming.
我们要没时间了
We're running out of time.
警告  接近量子虚无
Warning, approaching quantum void.
我来找你了  亲爱的
I'm coming to you, honey.
伙计们
Guys.
你们不需要实验室的遥控器吗  在我这里呢
Don't you need the remote to the lab? I just found it.
没有遥控器不能放大实验室
We can't grow the lab without it.
快拿过来
Get it to us fast.
可货车撞坏了
Yeah, but the van is busted.
用香车收纳盒
Use the Hot Wheels Rally case.
什么
What?
我爱你  皮姆博士
I love you, Dr. Pym.
遥控器  我们缺了遥控器
The remote! We're missing the remote!
你得去货车上看看
You gotta check the van!
赞
Awesome!
我在太平洋路上
I'm going down Pacific.
伯奇的人对我紧追不舍
Burch's boys are all over me.
我就到
I'm on my way.
好  我去拿实验室
Right. I'll get the lab.
太厉害了
Oh, that's badass!
厉害
Nice.
弹
Doink!
过来  你个小混蛋
Come here, you little weasel!
不  你别想
No, you don't!
看来你是可以的
I guess maybe you do.
拜托
Come on!
有人看见一个南方人抱着栋楼吗
Anyone see a Southern gentleman carrying a building?
他哪来的时间买票啊
How'd he even have time to buy a ticket?
你能不能就
Would you just one time,
好用一次
please work!
太好了
Yes!
好  我需要帮助
All right, I need help.
好
Yes!
真遗憾
Sorry.
再来个...
Somebody!
搞什么啊
Come on, man!
怎么能这样
Not cool!
杀人犯
Murderers!
太好了
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
我要喊你蚁东尼奥·班德拉斯
I'm gonna call you Ant-onio Banderas!
安东尼奥·班德拉斯  西班牙猛男影星
你太狠了
You're a badass!
太好了
Yes!
不不不
No, no, no!
蚁东尼奥
Ant-onio!
我们的朋友  驼背鲸
Our friends, the humpbacks,
会在旧金山湾戏水
dip in here to the San Francisco Bay
既是玩耍  也是为交配
for a little leisure and a little breeding.
听着  乌兹曼
Listen, Uzman...
或许它们这会儿就在下面  玩得正欢
And perhaps they're down below as we speak, doing the nasty.
去海滨跟我碰面
Just meet me at the waterfront.
三小时后
In three hours.
各位  我们才刚出港口
Folks. We've barely left the dock...
但似乎就有什么跟来了
but it looks like we got some company.
看啊  就在那里  看到了吗
Look. Right there. Do you see it, folks?
出现了  它出水了
There it is. There's a breach.
什么啊
What the...?
抱歉
Sorry.
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay!
抱歉  我知道我不是鲸鱼  我马上就好的
Sorry, I know I'm not a whale. This will just take a second.
那不是你的
That doesn't belong to you!
不不不
No, no! No, no!
你这是在自讨没趣
You're embarrassing yourself now.
快放手吧
Come on. Let go.
谢谢
Thank you.
这个我拿了
I'll take this now.
那会模糊你的意识
It melts your mind.
你脑袋里放了信息
A message in your head.
我做了个梦
I had a dream.
爸爸  妈妈在哪
Daddy? Where's Mommy?
我们玩时  我每次都藏在那里
It's where I hid every time that we played.
我爱你  汉克
I love you, Hank.
爸爸
Daddy?
爸爸  怎么回事
Dad? What's going on?
你怎么还没找到妈妈
Why haven't you found Mom?
你似乎迷路了  汉克  你没事吧
You look lost, Hank. Are you all right?
还觉得你无所不知吗  汉克
Still think you have all the answers, Hank?
是我
It's me.
真对不起
I'm so sorry...
这么久才找到你
it took so long.
不
No.
你现在来了
You're here now.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
我以为我完了
I thought I was gone.
但你手里发出的那股能量
But that energy from your hands...
你怎么做到的
how did you do that?
我已经不是30年前的那个女人了  亨利
I'm not the same woman I was 30 years ago, Henry.
这地方
This place...
会改变你
it changes you.
适应是一方面  但也有
Adaptation is part of it, but some of it is...
进化
evolution.
实验室坐标未找到
Lab coordinates not found.
不能上升
Do not ascend.
我或许该跟你说说上面的情况
I should probably tell you what we're dealing with up there.
我拿到实验室了
I got the lab. I got the lab.
让开  让开
Move. Move.
让开
Move!
让让路
Get out of the way.
我们走
Let's go.
似乎没人知道这是什么
No one here appears to be sure what this is.
它至少要有80到85英尺
It's gotta be 80-85 feet tall.
快让开
Get out of the way!
我拿到实验室了
I got the lab.
空气好厚
The air feels chunky.
不  他太大了
Oh, no. He's too big.
斯科特
Scotty!
Scott!
我要睡了
I'm gonna go to sleep.
我就睡个五分钟
I'm just gonna go to sleep now for five minutes.
我就想睡五分钟
I just need five minutes.
五分钟
Five minutes!
你把实验室拿去安全的地方
You get the lab somewhere safe.
-斯科特要没气的  -好
- Scott's air won't last. - Okay.
走开
Move!
让开  让开
Move! Move!
不  等等
No, wait!
实验室已恢复
Lab at full scale.
他们做到了
They did it.
可以上升
Ready to ascend.
我们去见女儿吧
Let's go see our daughter.
斯科特
Scott!
斯科特  快醒醒
Scott, come on, wake up!
快点  你在哪  斯科特
Come on. Come on, where are you, Scott?
找到你了
Gotcha.
斯科特
Scott?
斯科特  霍普  回复
Scotty! Hope, come in.
你们被楼压垮了吗
Did you get crushed by the building?
遥控器呢  路易斯
Where's the remote, Luis?
可能在那里
It's probably in there.
不在我这儿
I don't have it. I don't have it.
看来我们要说
I guess this is where we say
再见了  哥们
Adios, amigo.
不不不
No, no, no, no!
谢谢  伙计们
Thanks, guys.
艾娃
Ava?
Ava!
艾娃
就要可以提取了
Almost ready for extraction.
请停下  都有人受伤了
Please, stop! People are getting hurt!
一切都疼  别跟我提痛苦
Everything hurts. Don't talk to me about pain!
如果汉克是对的呢
What if Hank is right?
如果这个过程会害死珍妮特呢
What if this process kills Janet?
怎么  你还担心她
What, you're worried about her?
我只是说  她是个厉害的科学家
All I'm saying is that she is a brilliant scientist.
她或许能帮你
She may be able to help.
她会帮我的  就现在
Oh, she will help. Right now!
如果她死了  就死吧
And if she dies, she dies!
不  对不起  我们不能这么做
No, no. I'm sorry, we can't do this.
我们得另找办法
We have to find another way.
这就是办法
This is the way.
珍妮特
Janet!
她开始提取了
She started the extraction.
她会撕碎我妈妈的
She's gonna tear Mom apart.
不
No!
霍普
Hope!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
妈妈
Mom?
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们找到你了
We found you.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
我也想你  小糖豆
I missed you too, Jellybean.
没事了
It's okay.
我回来了  我们有时间了
I'm here now. We have time.
再也不要临时出差了  好吗
No more last-minute business trips, okay?
我保证
I promise.
不  没事的
No, it's okay!
没事  别担心我
It's all right. Just don't worry about me.
-我会没事的  -爸爸
- I'll be fine. - Dad.
斯科特
Scott.
凡·戴恩女士
Miss Van Dyne.
很高兴...
It's nice to...
我们也算是认识了
Well, I guess we've already met.
是啊  我们是见过
Yeah. I guess we have.
等等
Wait.
你的痛苦
Your pain.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
好疼啊
It hurts.
一直都在疼
It always hurts.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我觉得我能帮你
I think I can help you.
你知道她能那么做吗
Did you know she could do that?
没事了
It's okay.
伙计们  警察要来了
Guys, the cops are coming!
警察要来了  全要来了
The cops are coming. Like, all of 'em!
-我得走了  -我们都得走了
- I gotta go. - We gotta go!
他们怎么办
What about them?
手举起来
Hands in the air!
-不  我们只是在做我们的工作  -不
- No! We are going to our jobs. - No.
我们看到他们想冲人开枪
You see, we see these guys. They trying to shoot people.
我们就逮捕了他们  为你们  不客气
So we apprehended them. For you. You're welcome.
我们贩卖被盗科技产品
We traffic in stolen technology.
我们还杀了好多人
And we have killed many, many people.
他是带头的
He's in charge.
是的  是我
That's true, I am.
我的餐馆还违反了多条卫生法规
I've also committed numerous health code violations in my restaurant.
有些说出来能吓你一跳
Some of them would shock you.
还真是吐真剂
It is truth serum.
我们得离开
We gotta get outta here.
马上
Fast.
我有主意
I have an idea.
巨人被发现位于
Giant figure, now spotted
百老汇和拉古娜街街口
at the intersection of Broadway and Laguna.
各单位前往
All units move in.
快走
Go, go!
他在那里
There he is!
结束了  斯科特
It's over, Scotty!
对不起  但我们抓到你了
I'm sorry, but we got you, man!
拜托  结束了  哥们
Come on. It's the end of the line, pal.
你无处可躲了
There's nowhere to hide.
赶紧认输吧  没事的
Just pull off that Band-Aid! You lost! It's okay!
该死  斯科特  缩小自己
Damn it, Scotty, reduce yourself!
魔术
Magic.
该死
Damn it!
去朗家  马上
Get to Lang's, now!
好样的  亲爱的
Well done, honey.
我们走
Let's go!
你走吧
Leave me here.
我们可以逃走的
We can make it.
你也说过
You said it yourself.
我伤害过人
I've hurt people.
但你没有
But you haven't.
走吧  求你
Go. Please!
我们可以的  艾娃
We can make it, Ava.
比尔
Bill...
我不会离开你的
I'm not leaving you.
你们好啊
Oh, hey, guys.
我的两年这就结束了吗
Are my two years up already?
外面世界什么样啊
What's it like out there?
大家还跳舞吗
I mean, do people still dance?
还有流动餐车这回事吗
Are food trucks still a thing?
你这次是逃脱了  斯科特
Well, you got away with it this time, Scott, but...
我们会再见的
I'll be seeing you again.
在哪
Where?
我们要在哪再见
Where will you be seeing me again?
就是...泛泛地说
Like, in general...
下次你再干坏事
The next time you do something bad,
我就会抓到你
I'll be there to catch you...
你会关注...
You'll be watching...
我以为你是想邀请我去哪
I thought you were inviting me somewhere.
我为什么要那么做
Why would I do that?
我也想啊  你为什么要那么做啊
That's what I was wondering, why would you do that?
去派对  吃饭吗
Like a party, or like, dinner or something?
我不知道  我以为你都计划好了
I don't know. I thought you planned the evening.
不  我是"回头再逮你"的意思
No, I meant, "I'll arrest you later, again."
当然  不然就太奇怪了
Of course, that would be strange.
-你保重  吉米  -好
- Take it easy, Jimmy. - Okay.
你想一起吃个饭吗
Did you want to grab dinner, or something?
我也没事...
I mean, because I'm free...
算了  走吧
Yeah. Come on.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Yeah!
那是我们  需要帮助吗
Yes, that was us. How can I help you?
前科范安保
X-Con Security.
卡拉佩特安先生
Mr. Karapetyan?
嗯  你看到了
Yeah, you saw that?
我们也很荣幸跟您做生意
It would be an honor to be in business with you as well.
周二早9点见  好
I'll see you Thursday, 9:00 AM. Okay.
太好了
Yeah!
就这样谈生意
That's how you close a deal!
太棒了
This is awesome.
凯西
So, Cassie...
你长大后想做什么
what do you want to be when you grow up?
我想帮助他人
I wanna help people...
像我爸爸那样
like my dad.
真的吗
Really?
我本想做他的搭档
I wanted to be his partner.
但他说他想要你
But he said he wants you.
是吗
Is that so?
爸爸
Daddy!
等等
Hold on.
闪开啦
Move, get outta here!
斯科特  别别别
Scott, don't, don't, don't!
恶心
Oh, gross!
蛾子的灰好讨厌
I hate that moth dust!
快走  走开
Go! Shoo! Shoo!
蚁人2: 黄蜂女现身
我曾是一位受尊敬的科学家
I used to be a respected scientist.
名字被挂在大楼上
I had my name on the sides of buildings.
现在  却是这样
Now, I got this.
是你想要小一点的量子隧道
Well, you wanted a smaller quantum tunnel.
这不就小点了吗
This is... smaller.
抱歉  怪我
Sorry. My bad.
我觉得它还挺有特点
I think it has flair.
好了  控制已上线
All right. Control's online.
收集罐要以去耦的方式启动
The collection unit activates when you decouple it.
它应该会自动开始吸收量子治愈粒子
It should automatically start absorbing quantum healing particles.
另外  别靠近缓步动物场
Also, make sure you stay out of the tardigrade fields.
它们虽然可爱  但会吃了你
They're cute, but they'll eat you.
别被吸入时间涡旋
And don't get sucked into a time vortex.
我们会无法救你的
We won't be able to save you.
好吧
Okay.
进入亚原子状态  倒计时五
Going subatomic in five...
四
four...
三
three...
二
two...
一
one.
好了  斯科特  检查通讯
All right, Scott, this is a mic check.
检查通讯  一二  一二
Mic check, one, two. One, two.
量子域的各位今天怎么样啊
How's everybody doing tonight in the quantum realm?
斯科特  我们收到了
Scott, we read you.
我就是想确认嘛
I just wanna make sure.
好了
Okay.
为我们的新幽灵朋友拿到治愈粒子了
Healing particles secured for our new Ghost friend.
很好
Great.
准备冲进入  倒计时
Preparing for re-entry in...
五  四  三
five, four, three...
喂
Hello?
真好笑
Very funny.
汉克  别闹了
Hank, quit screwing around.
你还叫我别闹呢
You told me yourself not to screw around.
汉克
Hank?
霍普
Hope?
珍妮特
Janet.
伙计们
Guys.
好了  说真的  别闹啊
Okay, seriously, don't joke around.
把我弄回去  快点
Bring me up, let's go.
伙计们
Guys!